DANIJEL LAKIC

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science And Programming, Expected

in 06/2023

Mid Sweden University - Östersund, Sweden

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable employee seeking developer position. Offering excellent communication and good judgment. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Programmer with over 2 years of experience in developing as from university education as well as onside private projects. Excellent at resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

WORK HISTORY

Supervisor, 11/2015 - Current

SWEDEN MIGRATION AGENCY, Stockholm, SE

- Handled customer complaints, resolved issues, and adjusted policies to meet changing needs.
- Protected facility and property clients by regularly circulating premises and monitoring surveillance feeds.
- Contacted law enforcement in case of unauthorized persons, documents, and materials.

Frontend Developer Trainee 05/2022 - 07/2022

Brainnest, Stockholm, SE

• The Brainnest Frontend Development Industry Training

Care Assistant, 09/2013 - 10/2015

FANCY CARE AB, Stockholm, SE

- Ran errands for patients, did shopping, and picked up other necessities.
- Scheduled and accompanied clients to medical appointments.
- Monitored and maintained cleanliness, sanitation, and organization of assigned station and service areas.
- Planned, prepared, and served meals and snacks according to prescribed diets.

- Stockholm Sweden
- 0705889765
- danijellakic@yahoo.com

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://www.danijellakic.com/ Website under construction
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/danij el-lakic-9133b8143/

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, C#
- JS Framework: React
- Database SQL, MySQL
- Responsive Web Design
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Agile Workflow

LANGUAGES

Serbian:	Swedish:
Bilingual or Proficient (C2)	Bilingual or Proficient (C2)
English:	Spanish:
Bilingual or Proficient (C2)	Upper intermediate (B2)